字幕转制｜天外生物
感谢原字幕制作者
了不起的菲丽西
♫ 你知道该做些什么 ♫
♪ You'll know the right words ♪
♫ 好的想法就在你心中 ♫
♪ They're all in your head ♪
♫ 所以当清晨来临时，振奋精神整装待发吧 ♫
♪ So wake up in the morning and get out of bed ♪
♫ 你所拥有的梦想 ♫
♪ The dreams you've been dreaming ♪
♫ 现在正要实现 ♫
♪ Well, right now's the time ♪
♫ 你所创造的巨兽 ♫
♪ You build up these monsters ♪
♫ 它们都潜藏在你的意识里 ♫
♪ They're just in your mind ♪
♫ 如果你的内心感受到了 ♫
♪ If you feel it in your heart ♪
♫ 那么就大声唱出来吧 ♫
♪ Then sing it loud ♪
♫ 哦~哦~ ♫
♪ Oh, oh, oh Oh, oh, oh ♪
♫ 我知道你清楚自己是谁，所以大声唱出来吧 ♫
♪ I know you know who you are, So sing it loud ♪
♫ 它原本就为你谱写 ♫
♪ It's all about you ♪
♫ 你必须相信 ♫
♪ You just gotta know, gotta know ♪
♫ 你已经可以独当一面 ♫
♪ You can do it on your own ♪
♫ 这就是为什么我要写这首歌 ♫
♪ Guess that's why I wrote this song... ♪
♫ 它原本就为你谱写，只为你谱写 ♫
♪ You know it's about you, It's always about you ♪
♫ 所以勇往直前吧 ♫
♪ So let it go. ♪
再见了，孤儿院
Bye-bye, orphanage!
慢慢来，就快到了
Slowly! Almost there!
立定
Stop!
嘘
Shhh!
哼
Ha!
菲丽西又去哪了
Where is Felicie?
呃，先生，我也不知道
Uh, sir, I don't know.
你在看什么呢，臭小子
What are you looking at,you idiot?
喔
Whoa!
快去找到她
Go get Felicie!
可您让我去哪儿找啊
You know, I'm having a little bit of trouble knowing which direction...
现在就去！
Now!
恶 ！
Ugh!
哦好痛
Ouch! Ah!
维克多
Victor!
拉我一下
Can you help me?
哼
Ha!
你别再闹别扭了
Stop! Stop doing your grumpy face!
我并没有，我只是有点在意
I'm not, I'm just a little bit hurt that you were...
你居然想丢下我独自逃跑
..I don't know, escaping without me!
逃跑？我想逃跑？
Escaping? Me?
不，我只是想上去看看这美丽的景色
No, I was just looking at the spectacular view!
你知道的，如果没有我陪你的话
Because, you know, you wouldn't last
外面的世界可是很危险的
more than five minutes out there without me.
哼 哈
Ha! Ha!
快住手 你知道这样做也很危险
Don't start! You know how this ends.
我们是同时来到这个鬼地方的
We arrived at the same time,
我们也要同时逃出去
and we'll escape at the same time.
我发誓
I promise!
随你说咯
OK!
嘿，维克多，接着
Hey, Victor! Hiyah!
哦不，又开始了
Oh, no! Here we go!
喔 喔
Whoo! Whoo!
喔
Whoo!
♫ 你必须相信 ♫
♪ You just gotta know, gotta know ♪
♫ 你已经可以独当一面 ♫
♪ You can do it on your own ♪
♫ 这就是为什么我要写这首歌 ♫
♪ Guess that's why I wrote this song... ♪
♫ 它原本就为你谱写，只为你谱写 ♫
♪ You know it's about you, It's always about you ♪
喔 喔
Whoo-hoo!
♫ 所以勇往直前吧 ♫
♪ So let it go. ♪
这是最后一次原谅你们了
This is the last time!
我们真的感到很抱歉
We're sorry- We're sorry, and...
行行行，放开他们
Tut-tut-tut! Let them go!
你，回到你的房间
You, go to your room.
谢谢你 谢谢你 院长嬷嬷
Thank you! Thank you, Mother Superior.
行了，快回去
Enough. Go to your room.
容我说一句您今天看起来
And may I just say that you are looking very...
够了
Enough..
非常光彩照人
Superior today.
不要再说了
Enough!
好吧
OK!
菲丽西，我知道你梦想成为一个芭蕾舞演员
Felicie, I know you have this dream of being a dancer.
我们都知道
We all know it!
但是我
But I...
停停停，所有人都有梦想
Tut-tut-tut! All the world has a dream.
但是记住我这句话，梦无法成真
But get this into your head, dreams are not reality.
梦想终究会被埋葬 因为生活是
Dreams are buried because life is
艰辛的，残酷的，没有人会同情你
hard, brutal and without pity.
可是
But...
得得得
Tut-tut-tut!
你记住了没有
Agreed?
记住了
Agreed.
在巴黎有一所舞蹈学校，小姑娘
A dance school in Paris, little lady,
它叫巴黎歌剧院
the Opera de Paris,
那里全是舞蹈演员和舞蹈
full of dancers and dance!
你从哪找到这个的
Where did you find this?
我自有办法
I have my sources.
怎么样，看够了吧
OK? Enough!
我能再看一下吗
Can I see it again?
不行
No.
求你了
Please!
不行，除非你和我今晚能逃出去，我向你保证
No, but if you escape with me tonight, you have my word.
我会带你去这个舞蹈学校
I will take you to this dance school,
你会成为最伟大的的舞蹈家
and you will become the greatest dancer,
而我会成为最伟大的发明家
And I will become the greatest inventor ever!
那么说 你有计划了
Do you have a plan?
一个聪明绝顶的计划
A brilliant plan!
集合了本天才毋庸置疑的才华与智慧
A plan worthy of my total, utter, unquestionable genius.
让我看看
Let me see.
等我们逃出去再看
After we escape.
不行
No!
给我 我要看
Now! Now!
都说了现在不行
I said after.
现在就看
Now!
不行
After !
现在就看嘛
Now!
不行不行
After !
噢
Ow!
巴黎的舞蹈学校
A dance school in Paris.
嗯
Hmm.
嘘，是我，快跟我来
Shhh! It's me! Come on!
啊 我的天
Oh, my!
你的绝妙计划里还有只鸡
Is a chicken part of your brilliant plan?
没错
Affirmative!
好极了
Great!
哦额
Aaah!
院长嬷嬷让我带这个逃跑的孩子
I'm taking this pitiful deserter
去见她
to Mother Superior.
没问题 修女
OK, Sister. Hmm...
嗯～
Hmm?
啊
Ahh!
紧急情况 警报 启动备用计划
Emergency! Emergency! Activate Plan B!
从这走
This way!
执行备用计划
Activate Plan B!
这就是你无与伦比的计划？
That was your best ever plan?
你别这么挑剔好吗
You are so critical!
你真是个差劲的逃跑家
And you're a terrible escaper!
“逃跑家”根本就不是个词
'Escaper' is not a word!
噢天，又撞了一次
Ow! God, not again!
都给我下来
Get back down here!
给我把门打开
Open this door!
这三个月来
For the last three months,
我一直在研究母鸡
I have been studying chickens.
我知道了它们怎么进食
I know how they eat.
给我把门打开
Open this door!
我知道了它们怎么走路
I know how they walk.
我还知道它们如何下蛋
I know how they lay an egg.
我现在可以说对它们是完全了解的
There is nothing about a chicken that I do not know!
哒哒
Ta-da!
这就是我发明的“鸡翼”
I call them chicken wings!
可是 鸡根本不会飞啊
Chickens don't fly!
可它们有翅膀 一定会飞的
But they have wings. They must fly.
你会飞，对吧
You fly, don't you?
飞吧
Fly!
啊哦
Uh-oh!
终于逮到你们了
I'm going to... Got you
跟我回去 你们两个小鬼
Come here, you rascals!
后会无期了
Goodbye!
什么
What?
让我们飞吧
Let's go!
咯咯哒
Cock-a-doodle-doo!
总有一天 人们会这样出行
One day, everyone will travel like this!
噢
Ow!
我的音乐盒
My music box!
维克多 他追来了
Victor! He's behind you!
快给我停下 你们是逃不掉的
I've got my eye on you! You're not going anywhere!
哦不
Aaah! Oh no!
抓紧了
Hang on!
谢谢
Thanks!
小心前面
Victor, watch out!
哈哈 现在你们哪也去不了了吧
Yeah! Ha-ha! Now I've got you!
看到你们了
I see you!
快点儿 跟我来
This way! Let's go!
等等我 哦不 快点儿
Wait! Oh! Oh, no!
快抓住我的手
Yah! Grab on! Grab on!
放手
Oh! Let me go! Let him go!
放开我 你这个坏蛋
Let me go, stinky!
啊
Oh!
还算顺利吧
That went well, no?
你可真棒
You're unbelievable.
那当然了
I know.
维克多 我们居然逃出来了
Victor, we actually did it!
是啊 我们居然逃出来了
Yes, we actually did!
噢 它坏了
Oh.
没关系 我可以修好它
I can fix this.
我想说的是
But I should say
因为当初
that seeing as this is the one thing
它和你一起被留在了孤儿院门口
That was in your crib when you were left outside the orphanage,
你真的应该小心保管它
you should take a teeny-tiny, eensy-weensy
别让它受到磕碰
little bit more care of it.
修好了 不用谢我
Fixed! Don't thank me!
等到了明天 巴黎
And tomorrow, chérie, Paris...
将会成为我们的舞台
..will be ours.
早安 我的公主
Good morning, sunshine!
恶 你是有多久没刷牙了
Eww! When's the last time you brushed your teeth?
这边 这个箱子
Start with this one.
喔
Whoa!
哦
Ugh!
我们到哪儿了
I can't see where we are.
别担心 我们在巴黎
Relax! We're in Paris!
呃
Aaah!
安静 你想被抓住吗
Quiet! We're going to get caught!
不准再出声了
Not another noise out of you.
不是我放的
That wasn't me!
哇
Wow!
这儿就是巴黎
It's incredible!
巴黎太美了
Paris is amazing.
巴黎这么大 可舞蹈学校在哪儿呢
So, where's the dance school?
别担心 菲丽西
Relax, Felicie!
好好享受吧 这可是梦想之都巴黎啊
Enjoy Paris. Breathe it in.
你好吗
Hi there!
您的小胡子不错啊
Love your moustache, monsieur!
啊 这就是巴黎
Ah, yes, Paris!
这里有浪漫 这里有梦想
City of romance. City of dreams.
这里有名望与财富
City of fame and fortune!
还有 路灯和鸽子
City of lamp posts. City of pigeons.
浪漫说过了吗
Did I say romance?
是的 说过了 那舞蹈学校在哪儿呢
Yes, you did. Now, where's the dance school?
呃…我不知道
Uh, I don't know.
没关系 我们是伙伴
Don't worry. We're a team.
我们一起去找
We'll find it together.
呃
Ugh!
你不觉得这样逃出来有点太鲁莽了
Do you think it was stupid to come to Paris?
别这样说 我们可不能因为这点小事就轻言放弃
Don't say that! We should never give up on our dreams.
可我们只是孤儿 对巴黎一无所知
We're kids! We're all alone.
或许我梦想成为舞蹈家 真的是异想天开呢
Was I really crazy to think I could be a dancer?
你觉得呢
What do you think?
维克多？
Victor?
唉我说
I said...
维克多？
Victor?
我没事
I'm OK!
你去那做什么 快回来
Come back!
可我不会游泳
I can't swim!
明早七点 在这座桥上等我 我们不见不散
Meet me on this bridge at this time tomorrow.
无论遇到什么情况
No matter how dangerous it is,
我一定会到的
I will return!
维克多
Victor!
你快回来
Come back!
别丢下我
Don't leave!
求你了
Please.
嗯
Huh?
[每个女生都值得拥有一套宝诗龙首饰]
嗷
Aaah!
给我老实交代
What have you come here to do, huh?
你来这儿想偷什么
You came here to steal, didn't you?
告诉我 你这个贼
Answer me! You're a thief!
我没想偷东西 我只是在看她跳舞
I wasn't stealing! I was looking at the dancer!
别想撒谎 把东西拿出来
Liar! Empty your pockets!
放开我
Get off me!
你想得美
Oh, yeah?
住手 放开她
Leave her alone.
她是个小偷
She came here to steal!
我不是 我没有偷东西
I didn't! I really didn't!
先想清楚
Think this through.
如果你指认她是小偷 那你得向院长解释一下
If you hurt her, then you will have to explain
她是怎么溜进来的
how she got here in the first place,
而你 守门人 那时到哪里去了
and aren't you supposed to be taking care of the building?
D你能承担起这个责任吗
o you really want to take the fall for this?
别挡路
Clear off.
等一下
Wait!
快走吧 离开这里
Go. Get out of here.
我可没什么让你偷
I have nothing to steal!
我这样 说不出话来
I-I can't sp... I can't speak!
我只是想说 谢谢你救我一命
I just wanted to say thank you for saving me!
你谢过了 好自为之吧
You've said it. Have a nice life.
请问 刚才跳舞的人是谁啊
Excuse me, but who was that dancer on stage?
罗西塔莫里 芭蕾舞明星
Rosita Mauri, top dancer at the Opera.
哇
Wow!
刚才她做出的那个惊人的跳跃 这是太美了
And what she did - that crazy jumpy thing, what was that?
你也是个舞蹈演员吗？
Are you a dancer too?
我只是个清洁工 你真的有点烦
I'm a cleaner, and you are an irritation.
别再跟着我了
Go away.
可您是在这儿第一个
But you're the first person
对我这么好的人
to show me any kindness in this city.
我和同伴走丢了
I've been separated from my best friend.
我现在无家可归
I have nowhere to go,
而且我是个孤儿 拜托
and I'm an orphan.
是很可怜 可我讨厌小孩儿
Nice try, but I hate kids,
尤其是孤儿
especially orphans.
给我让开
Go find another idiot.
擦楼梯去 奥黛特
The stairs, Odette.
它们脏兮兮的 丢我的脸
The stairs are a disgrace.
明天还有客人来呢
I have guests tomorrow afternoon,
我要你把房子彻底打扫得焕然一新 听见了吗
and I want my building looking worthy top to bottom.
是的 夫人
I understand, ma'am.
既然你听清了
If you understand,
打扫干净之前不准休息
why are you entering your rooms?
我来帮您吧
Let me help you!
别碍事
Get out of here!
但您需要我 帮您打扫
You need me. I can clean.
我可以打扫得非常干净
In fact, 'Squeaky Clean' is my middle name.
我还年轻 腿脚灵活 不像您一样…
I'm young. My legs work. Yours don't.
呃我是说 我可以帮您非常轻松地完成工作啊
Uh, it's gonna feel so much easier with me helping.
还要我请你进来吗
Are you coming?
哇 这儿台阶真多
Whoa! That's a lot of stairs.
您在这里工作吗
Are you the caretaker?
是的 你在能够独立生活之前 可以暂住在我这里
Yes. And you can stay with me until you get on your feet,
但有个条件 别再问问题了
On one condition -no more questions.
那我可以住多久呢
How long can I stay?
又来 问个没完
Ugh. That was a question.
对了 刚才那位很凶的夫人是谁啊
By the way, who was that witch?
雷吉纳勒奥 这座房子的主人
Regine Le Haut. She owns this building.
她就喜欢吃你这种红头发马尾辫的小女孩儿
And she eats ginger orphans with ponytails.
快干活吧
Now, clean!
哈哈
Ha!
嗯？
Huh?
您在这工作多久了
How long have you worked here?
我该怎么称呼您呢 您有绰号吗 我有个绰号 您想听吗
Do you have a nickname? Wanna know mine?
我有单人床睡吗
Will I have my own bed?
您夜里不打呼噜的吧 您起床早吗
Do you snore? Are you a morning person?
您最喜欢什么水果啊
What's your favourite fruit?
我们早餐吃什么啊 我喜欢面包配果酱
What do you have for breakfast? I love baguette and jam.
您知道吗 我是因为想跳舞才逃出了孤儿院
You know I escaped from the orphanage to become a pupil at the Opera.
真的吗？
Did you?
您在那儿工作 应该也有认识的人吧
You work there, so you must know people.
您能帮帮我吗
Could you help me?
你可别指望我
Don't hold your breath.
昨晚那支舞真是太美了
What that étoile did yesterday,oh, it was so magical.
我喜欢跳舞 您也会跳舞吗
I love dancing. Do you love dancing?
是因为你脚瘸了吗
Is that because you've got a limp?
起来
Get up
是的 夫人
Yes, ma'am.
她是谁
Who is this?
谁也不是 她来帮忙的
No-one. She helps.
那你养她 自己出钱
You feed it out of your wages.
好的 夫人
Yes, ma'am.
我要你把桌布烘干熨好 快去
I want you to air and press the linen. Now!
嗯～
Hmm...
还不够干净
It's not clean.
嗯？
Huh?
喔
Whoa!
喔 哦
Whoa! Oh!
噢
Oh! Whoa!
你好啊
Hello!
不知道仆人进来要先敲门吗 你是谁
Servants are supposed to knock. Who are you?
我叫菲丽西 是来帮奥黛特打扫卫生的
I'm Felicie. I work with Odette. I clean.
♫ 哒哒哒 ♫
♪ Da da da da... ♪
那我先告退了 回头见
OK! I'm done. 'Bye now!
站住 小耗子，你刚刚在偷看 对不对？
Wait, little rat! You were spying, weren't you?
怎么会 我没有
I don't think so.
不 你就是
Yes, you were.
你从没见过如此美丽的舞姿才会偷看的
You were admiring the most wonderful dancer you've ever seen.
是不是这样 小耗子
Isn't that so, little rat?
别说了 你还不是最棒的舞者
You're not THE most wonderful dancer.
昨天晚上我看到的…
Yesterday I saw...
不得无礼
Don't be insolent!
你也是芭蕾舞演员吗
Are you a ballet dancer?
现在还不是 不过很快就是
I will be.
我和妈妈正等着
Mother and I are waiting
巴黎歌剧院寄来的录取通知书呢
for the letter that admits me to the Opera.
我很有天赋
I am so talented!
院长非常喜欢去我们家的餐厅用餐
Plus the director dines in my mom's restaurant,
因为那里有全巴黎最好吃的牛肋排
and he loves the prime rib.
很快 我就会成为全巴黎最有名的芭蕾舞之星
So this time next year, I shall be a famous ballerina.
芭蕾舞明星 真棒啊 那也是我的梦想
Ballerina! Me too!
来照照镜子 小耗子
Ha Reality check, little rat!
你没戏 只有我才能成为明星
You're nothing. I'm a star!
而你只配绕着我转
You're just orbiting around me.
那是什么？
What's that?
你是不是偷了我们家的东西
Have you stolen something from me?
没有啊
No.
给我看看
Show me! What is it?
那是妈妈留给我的音乐盒 非常珍贵
It's mine, and it's precious.
哦
Oh!
是啊
I'm sure.
那你去捡吧
Fetch!
不要
No!
哦 不
Oops!
哦
Oh!
从歌剧院寄来的雷吉纳勒奥夫人和卡米儿小姐的信件
A letter for Madame Regine Le Haut and Mademoiselle Camille from the Opera.
让我闻闻 信纸真香 带印花 蓝墨水儿
Hmm! Handmade paper! Embossed! Blue ink!
现在的小孩儿真没教养 哼
Oh, how rude! Children today have no manners!
[录取信 致卡米尔小姐]
把它拿来
Give me that!
你才不是卡米尔勒奥
You are not Camille Le Haut!
我就是啊
Of course I am.
又想骗我
No, you're not!
我看你这次想去警局
This time I call the police!
警局？ 我不要去警局 放开我
Police? Police? Why? No!
♫ 啦啦啦 ♫
♪ La la la la... ♪
出什么事了
What's going on here?
院长先生 她自称是卡米尔勒奥
Um, she says she's Camille Le Haut.
我看看 你说你是卡米尔勒奥吗
Hmm... Are you Camille Le Haut?
嗯…没错
Uh... yes?
哈哈哈 她就是卡米尔勒奥
Hmm...She IS Camille Le Haut!
做的不错 这没你什么事了 去干活吧
Return to your post, my friend.
好吧 我不管了
Alright, please yourselves.
幸会 勒奥小姐
Welcome, Miss Le Haut! Charmed!
幸会
Charmed!
我叫奥古斯特沃克贝伊
I am Auguste Emmanuel Vaucorbeil,
这所歌剧院的负责人
director of the Opera.
录取你是因为你妈妈的餐厅
You are here because your mother serves
有全巴黎最好吃的牛肋排
the best prime rib in Paris.
噢 希望你的舞姿也一样美
Oh! I hope you dance as well.
那当然了
Of course.
♫ 我至今都梦想 ♫
♪ When I look at my life ♪
♫ 成为一名舞者 大放异彩 ♫
♪ Wanna see myself shine on the dance floor ♪
♫ 但想要实现它 ♫
♪ But I won't get it right ♪
♫ 就必须忘忧消愁 心无旁骛 ♫
♪ Until I stop asking why and just let it go ♪
♫ 有时我想直面过去 迎向未来 ♫
♪ Sometimes I take a look at my life ♪
♫ 心有憧憬 ♫
♪ I take a look at my life ♪
♫ 想要精彩缤纷的生活 ♫
♪ And say oh, oh Wanna get it ♪
♫ 想要灿烂辉煌的人生 ♫
♪ Yeah, gotta get to the pot of gold ♪
♫ 想要寻找远方的彩虹 ♫
♪ Looking for the rainbow... ♪
♫ 想要穿越汹涌的风景 ♫
♪ To break the storm inside of me... ♪
我想你应该不是来学习芭蕾舞的吧
You're not a dancer, are you?
我是啊
Yes, I am!
真想不到
Who would've thought?
那就进去上课吧
Return to your class!
好的
OK!
史上最伟大的芭蕾舞大师
Oh, greatest ballet master of all time!
最有才华的芭蕾舞编舞 没有其他人能达到他的高度
Oh, most talented choreographer  in the universe and beyond!
他是那么英俊 那么高傲
He is handsome! He is elegant!
如此强势 如此权威 而这个人就在我面前
He is strong! He is powerful! He is the man!
我猜你有事找我帮忙
You want something from me?
你怎么知道
How did you know? Yes!
我录取了卡米尔勒奥 由你来教她
I have enrolled Camille Le Haut in your class.
还真是谢谢你了
Thank you.
♫ 想要寻找远方的彩虹 ♫
♪ Looking for the rainbow... ♪
♫ 想要穿越汹涌的风景 ♫
♪ To break the storm inside of me... ♪
♫ 就让彩虹 ♫
♪ The rainbow ♪
♫ 带走我内心的彷徨 ♫
♪ To take the clouds that are hiding me ♪
♫ 请治愈我满心的伤痕 ♫
♪ All I want is someone to heal the heart of me ♪
♫ 就让彩虹… ♫
♪ The rainbow... ♪
你好啊 你好
Hi! Hello!
呃 好吧
OK. Super.
我叫菲丽西
I'm Felicie!
菲丽西？
Felicie?
噢 不不不
Uh, no, no, no! No, sorry.
我很高兴能来到这里
I'm f-friendly, ever so friendly.
我的名字是卡米尔
And my name is Camille.
你好啊 我叫诺拉 不过大家都叫我诺哈
OK. I'm Nora, but everyone calls me Nora.
她们说这名字和我的脸很配
That's the name that goes with my face.
你该去热身了
Hey, you should warm up!
热身？
Warm up?
真不可思议 亲爱的
Oh, my! That is crazy!
我想你还是个新手吧
I'm guessing you're new, my darling.
你是怎么看出来的
You can tell that because...
他是谁啊
Who is that?
你在开玩笑么
You are joking, right?
他就是梅拉特先生
It's Louis Merante,
芭蕾舞大师级人物
ballet master, world-famous choreographer,
他曾经在独舞中跳出了最恐怖的弗韦泰转
the man who performed the most fouettés ever in a single solo.
孚维泰…？
Fou-whats?
就是旋转啦 特别难的旋转
Turns. Really difficult turns.
一共转了一百八十七圈 据说他一下台就吐了
187 in total, and right after, he vomited!
安静 孩子们 单手扶把准备
Silence, mam'selle! First position!
嗯？
Uh...
二位
Second!
什么
What?
三位
Third!
呃
Uh...
四位 收五位
Fourth, and rest in fifth!
啊 哦
Huh? Oh!
我要宣布一件大事
Today is an important day.
孩子们 你们将有机会
I've gathered all the coryphées together
出演《胡桃夹子》中的克拉拉一角
to audition for the part of Clara in 'The Nutcracker',
并与罗西塔莫里在平安夜一同演出
which will debut on Christmas Eve and star Rosita Mauri.
罗西塔 罗西塔莫里
Rosita? Rosita Mauri?
太好了 我简直不敢相信
Oh, I don't believe it!
你们都有机会得到这个角色
So every girl in this room has a chance to dance in my new ballet
除了你
except you.
你们每个人都很努力
You've all worked hard
除了你
except you.
你们由于出众的天赋与勇气来到了我的教室
You are here because of talent and guts.
除了我
Except me.
知道就好
Exactly!
从明天开始 我们将会进行选拔
Starting tomorrow, we'll have an audition.
每天都会淘汰你们其中之一
One of you will be eliminated each day.
所以 大小姐
So, tomorrow, little rich girl,
不管你托了谁的关系
no matter what strings you pulled to get here,
明天要走的人 就是你
that will be you!
可是我们家有全巴黎最好吃的牛肋排
But my mother serves the best prime rib in Paris!
我是素食主义者
I am a vegetarian.
一位 二位 嗯二位
First, second. Second.
不对 二位 三位…
No, second, third.
三…三位？
Third? Third?
三位 四位
Third, fourth.
五位
Fifth? Fifth.
一位 二位…
First. Second.
你好啊
Hello!
三位…
Third. Third?
下午好
Bonjour!
五位 六位
Fifth, sixth.
见到你很高兴
How are you?
不对 根本没有六位啊
There is no sixth.
好吧 我也很高兴见到你
Well, I'm happy to see you too.
嗨 维克多
Oh, Victor!
你好啊
Hello!
我有好多事要与你分享
I have so many things to tell you!
我也是
Me too.
这次可真是彻底坏了
Wow! This time, it's really broken.
你能修好它吗
Can you do something?
没问题 交给我吧
Don't worry, I've got it.
我可是在我们的小赌约里先拔头筹了
I am the winner of our little bet.
赌约？
What bet?
就是赌我们谁会先实现梦想啊
You know, the one about who gets their dream first.
我就要成为一名发明家啦
I am going to be an inventor!
真的？
Really?
你就羡慕我吧
You're just jealous that, in 24 hours,
我还找到了一份工作 而我的老板就是建…这个的
I've got a job with the man who is building that!
你不是掉到船上时摔到脑袋了吧
Did you bump your head when you fell in the boat?
呵呵
Nope!
你一定想不到我昨天经历了什么
Yesterday, after you got separated,
昨天与你分开之后
I just took a quiet walk around the streets of Paris.
我感到非常轻松惬意 十分开心
It was all good, totally good.
完全没感到害怕
I was really not scared at all.
这里的人也很友善 总给我指路
I met some charming locals who helped me find my way.
最不可思议的是
And you will never believe this,
我走到了一间酒吧里
but then I stumbled on a Breton bar
那里的人都很友善 给了我一个大大的拥抱
and I got a big, warm and friendly welcome.
他们像对待亲侄子…不对 亲儿子一样对待我
They welcomed me like a brother, a son, a nephew!
然后我就遇到了一个名叫马汀的家伙
And then I met this super guy called Mathurin.
我们有说有笑 又唱又跳
We talked, we laughed, we danced together,
我们就成了好哥们
and then my new best buddy and I
总之 玩够了我们就去他家了
decided to head home to his place.
更难以置信的是
And you are never, ever going to believe this
他的老板竟然就是古斯塔夫埃菲尔
but he works in the atelier of Gustave Eiffel,
一位绝无仅有的 慧眼独具的
the nicest, best
才华横溢的
and most magnetic inventor
世界上最伟大的发明家
in the whole world!
我做梦都想不到
I am going to be
我可以在这样一位世界闻名的工程师手下工作
the most famous engineer's right-hand man.
哦对了 我还会再想办法升级我的“鸡翼”
Oh, and I've gone back to square one with my chicken wings.
我现在正在研究纤维材质的空气集流系统
I am now working on combining air velocity with fibrous catchment systems.
也就是风筝
I'm trying a kite.
真棒啊 我也有了些进展
Wow! I made progress too!
比如说
Really?
我现在是巴黎歌剧院的学员 差不多算是吧
I'm a dancer. Yes! Yes! A student at the Opera.
马上我就会成为巴黎的芭蕾舞明星
And soon I'm going to be an étoile at the Opera de Paris.
你 现在是巴黎歌剧院的学员？
You, a dancer at the Opera?
是吗 那你跟我讲讲你是怎么混进去的
OK, and may I know how you came to be at the Opera?
走进去的啦 那里有灯光 还有…
By the door, I saw some lights and...
撒谎
Liar!
好吧 是卡米尔勒奥 就是她摔坏了我的音乐盒
OK! It's Camille Le Haut, the one who broke my music box.
还在撒谎
Liar!
她心存愧疚
She wanted to apologise
接着编啊
Liar!
先听我说完
Let me finish.
不听不听你撒谎
Liar, liar...
所以她想要把机会让给我
She gave me the letter that allowed her into the Opera.
你一撒谎 鼻子就会动
When you're lying, your nose shivers.
你真没劲
You're exhausting!
好吧 我冒充了她
I stole her identity.
什么 冒充别人 你是不是疯了
What? You stole it? Are you insane?
喔喔 哦不
Whoa! Whoa! Uh-oh!
啊～
Whoa!
维克多
Victor!
维克多 维克多
Victor! Victor!
啊
Whoa!
维克多
Victor!
你去哪儿 快回来
Come back! Don't leave!
我一定会回来的
I'll be back!
又来了
Again?
♫ 你会成就自我 ♫
♪ You're gonna be somebody ♪
♫ 明媚胜于花火 ♫
♪ You'll be bigger than Mars... ♪
♫ 你曾受尽冷落 ♫
♪ They might walk on you now ♪
♫ 但终将星光闪耀 ♫
♪ But they're walk-on, you're a star  ♪
♫ 与日争辉 实至名归 ♫
♪ You're gonna take on Titan like the champion you are ♪
♫ 誉满四海 声名远播 ♫
♪ From Ibiza to L.A. London to Qatar ♪
♫ 你将成就自我 ♫
♪ You'll be somebody... ♪
♫ 你将会成就自我 ♫
♪ You're gonna be somebody... ♪
♫ 荧惑亦不及你玫丽 ♫
♪ You'll be bigger than Mars ♪
♫ 你将成就自我 ♫
♪ You'll be somebody... ♪
好现在 下前叉
And to finish, the splits.
呃
Hmm?
现在 请起立
Now rise.
今天的课程结束了
The class is over,
宣布一下今天被淘汰的人 就是你
and the person who's leaving us today is you.
你很有热情与活力
You have the energy of a bullet,
可你的动作笨拙得像一头大象
but the lightness of a depressed elephant.
你现在可以走了
Pack your trunk!
呃～
Ahem!
请起立 孩子
Rise, please, mam'selle.
但是我觉得这样…还挺舒服的
But I like it here!
我说 请起立
Rise now!
我卡住了
I'm stuck!
送她去医院
Get her out of here.
您不是说一天只淘汰一个人的吗
Didn't you say one person per class?
好吧 今天你可以留下
Very well. Until the next audition.
但等到明天的课程结束 你一定会和我们说再见
Then it really will be bye-bye.
梅特拉先生讨厌我
Merante hates me.
别这么说 他对谁都这样
Don't say that. That's just his way.
不 他就是很讨厌你
No, she's right. He hates you.
他恨不得拿手杖敲碎你的膝盖骨
If he could, he'd smash your kneecaps with his cane.
我没机会了
Oh, I have no chance.
别这么说 机会永远都在
There's always a chance.
不一定
Not always.
有的时候你就是一点机会也没有
This might be one of those times there's no chance at all.
可我真的很想留下
But I really wanna stay here.
这样的话 你还有十二个小时可以练习 努力一下
Then you have 12 hours to work really hard, listen,
说不定会有进步呢
push yourself and then work some more.
这是谁啊
Who is that?
鲁迪 巴黎歌剧院芭蕾舞团最美颧骨奖得主
Rudi from the top boys class. Holder of the Best Cheekbones at the Opera award.
我喜欢她 看他那头阳光般的金发
I love him! He's so blond and shiny.
哦 哇
Oh, wow!
你就是新来的吗
Ooh! You are new, yes?
是啊
Yes.
她叫卡米尔 她有两只眼睛
he's Camille. She has two eyes.
呵 眼睛倒是挺有灵气的 可你的舞姿烂到没眼看
Ha! You have spirit, Camille, but your dancing sucks.
别和我抢！
It's mine!
他以为他是谁
Who does he think he is?
我们会再见面的 小美人
Until we meet again, Minoushka!
做梦去吧
Only in your dreams.
菲丽西
Felicie?
你为什么会在这
What are you doing here?
我可以解释
I can explain!
不必了
There is nothing to explain.
等等 别走
Wait! Wait!
真的对不起 我也不知道该怎样道歉才好
I'm sorry! Triple sorry.
真心感到抱歉
If there was a bigger word for 'sorry', I'd say it.
我收留你 你却用撒谎和冒名顶替来回报我
I let you into my life, and you lied to me.
我不喜欢撒谎的孩子
I don't like lies.
你会害我丢掉工作的
I could lose my job because of you.
真的对不起 我不该那样做的
I get it. I messed up.
我只是太渴望跳舞了
But you don't understand.
我从小就喜欢跳舞
Since I can remember, I've wanted to dance.
当我看到罗西塔莫里的舞姿时
And when I saw Rosita Mauri and she did those amazing moves,
我就知道我想成为她
I knew that's what I wanted to be.
想跳出像她那样优美而富有情感的舞蹈
I knew my dream could come true!
说起来您可能不信
I know it's hard to understand.
您不能再跳舞了
You hate dancing.
对此我真心感到惋惜
But I just want you to know I'm truly sorry.
信来了吗
Any mail?
没有信件 夫人
There is no mail.
信件一到 立刻送来
As soon as there is, fetch it.
你会跳舞吗
Can you dance?
会吧 我想还算会的
Yes. At least, I think I can.
明早五点开始训练
Training starts at 5am tomorrow.
您来教我吗
Are you a teacher?
你有的选吗
Do you have another option?
明早五点？
5am?
训练时间到
Time to train!
现在 跳起来摸这个铃铛
Jump and ring the bell!
摸它做什么？
Why?
按我说的做
Just do it.
你不是训练我跳舞的吗 ？
You don't want me to dance?
别问那么多 照做就是了
No talking. Jump and ring the bell!
再来
Again.
我们是要进行芭蕾训练的吧
You said we were going to train.
这就是 再来
This is it! Again!
嗯
Hmm!
哈哈
Ha!
菲丽西 你的动作毛躁毫无技巧可言
Felicie, you lack precision and finesse.
肢体协调性也不够
You have little or no sense of rhythm.
平衡感也有所欠缺 更别说优雅了
You're without balance, grace and charm.
不是吧 只跳两下就能看出这么多毛病 真的假的
Come on! You can't tell all that from one jump, can you?
好吧 你说的没错
You can.
你的优点是很有活力
On the good side, you have the energy of a bullet,
可你的动作却又笨拙得像头大象
but you also have the lightness of a depressed elephant.
天呐 梅特拉也这么说我 而且你们说的一字不差
Hey! Merante used exactly the same phrase!
毕竟在那里旁听多年 耳濡目染惯了
After 10 years of cleaning, you pick stuff up.
不说这个 现在跳起来摸铃铛
OK, now jump up, ring this bell,
落地时不许溅起水花
land and do not splash the water.
我怎么可能做到
But that's impossible.
你不去努力尝试 梦想永远无法实现
I thought it was your dream to dance.
好吧
OK!
我能行
Come on!
♫ 生活如此不公 ♫
♪ You're so unfair to yourself ♪
♫ 有时你这样想 ♫
♪ Got that feeling in your chest... ♪
♫ 也曾顾影自怜 ♫
♪ Can't look in the mirror... ♪
你们走开啦
Get lost.
♫ 也曾逃避现实 ♫
♪ Can't see who you are... ♪
走开啦
Get lost.
去去
Shoo! Shoo!
♫ 甚至想要乔扮旁人生活 ♫
♪ You wanna be somebody else ♪
♫ 每每举步维艰 ♫
♪ Every time you falter ♪
♫ 每每跌堕泥泞 ♫
♪ Every time you fall ♪
♫ 我仍可见前途所向 ♫
♪ I can still see the road ahead... ♪
♫ 你将成为闪耀的新星 ♫
♪ You'll be brighter than the stars ♪
♫ 你的魅力会令自己惊讶 ♫
♪ And you'll see how radiant you are ♪
♫ 我知道你心存疑惑 ♫
♪ I know you're full of doubt ♪
♫ 但别因此畏葸不前 ♫
♪ But don't let them bring you down ♪
♫ 因为你的热情沛莫能御 ♫
♪ 'Cause you're unstoppable ♪
♫ 如日方升 ♫
♪ Rising higher than the sun ♪
♫ 将疑惑抛诸脑后 ♫
♪ Climb away until they're gone ♪
♫ 平步青云 ♫
♪ Way up above the clouds ♪
♫ 从此不再犹豫彷徨 ♫
♪ They'll never bring you down 'cause you're unstoppable... ♪
你
You!
♫ 从此不再犹豫彷徨 ♫
♪ They'll never bring you down 'cause you're unstoppable... ♪
跳的可不是一点半点的差
That was not merely bad,
简直就是课堂的反面教材
it was a catastrophe wrapped in a disaster with a side order of bad.
回家吧 你没这个天赋
Ta-ta!
♫ 紧握命运 不再放手 ♫
♪ Hold on, don't let go... ♪
你 和我 一起去屋顶
You, me, up.
♫ 即使黑暗来临 你也会迸发光芒 ♫
♪ Even in the dark, you glow ♪
♫ 你将成为闪耀的新星 ♫
♪ You'll be brighter than the stars ♪
♫ 你的魅力会令自己惊讶 ♫
♪ And you'll see how radiant you are... ♪
这儿真美
It's incredible!
♫ 但别因此畏葸不前 ♫
♪ They'll never bring you down... ♪
♫ 因为你的热情沛莫能御 ♫
♪ 'Cause you're unstoppable... ♪
初次见面时我说的话有些无礼 请原谅我吧
Last time we met, I was so very rude.
自我介绍一下
Let me introduce myself.
我叫
I am
鲁道夫迪梅忒列夫斯坦尼斯拉夫阿列亚穆拉科夫斯基
Rudolph Dimitriev Stanislaw Artiem Rankovsky...
三世
..the Third.
你名字可真长
Big choice of names there.
别太担心 芭蕾之路并非易途
Don't worry.Everyone finds it hard at first.
可你我都是非凡的天才
But you and I are unique,
并不需要像普通人那样努力 不是吗
and we do not follow silly rules, yes?
哈 你这些花言巧语向来都很有用吧
How is that pick-up line working out for you?
你误会了 这些话我只会对你说 卡米尔
It is no line. I say it only to you, Camille.
只会对你说
Just to you.
跳吧
Et hop!
小心啊
Minoushka!
你没事吧
Uh, are you alright, Camille?
我没事
Yep! I'm OK!
那个叫鲁道夫的芭蕾舞演员
There's this boy, Rudolph, who, it turns out,
居然是俄罗斯王子
is a real Russian prince
他住在城堡里 养孔雀 有漂亮的高颧骨
with a castle and peacocks and cheekbones!
他带我去歌剧院屋顶
And he took me on the roof of the Opera,
然后这样看着我
and he was looking at me like this.
像这样
Then like this.
然后这样看着我
And then once like this.
等等 我有点乱 剧团里有男生 什么样的男生
Wait! Uh, a boy? What type of boy?
养孔雀 还有高颧骨
Peacocks? What type of cheekbones?
鲁道夫又是谁
And Rudolph?
他就是我的新朋友啊
He's a friend.
他说我一定会心想事成的
He says I'm gonna be everything I wanna be.
我也说过啊
I say that too!
可他说得特别深情
But he's deep as well.
好吧 深情…但 我有这个
Deep? Yeah, well, I have these.
哒嗒
Ta-da!
哦豁 你有扇铁门吗
Whoo-hoo. Doors.
没错 这扇门后就是埃菲尔先生的工作室
Yes, the doors to the atelier
他可真是个天才
of my new boss, engineer, genius.
要是你看到这门后的东西
If you saw what was behind these doors,
我就得杀你灭口…
I would have to kill you.
啊
Ahh!
糟糕 这下子你只有杀我灭口了
Looks like you're gonna have to kill me, then!
哦 我的天哪
Oh la la!
这是什么啊
What's that?
青春女神像
The Statue of Puberty,
它就要被运往美国
soon to go to America!
但这是一个大秘密
But it is a super secret,
所以你就当什么也没看过 明白吗
so you did not see it, OK?
好吧
OK.
这就是我的工作室
So, here's my office,
天才与伟大创意之家
the home of big ideas and genius.
比如说这个 这就是我设计的第三代“鸡翼”
For example, here we see the plans for chicken wings version 3.
啊～
Oh! Aaah! Ahem!
我和老板正在研究几项…
At the moment, my boss and I are working on several,
呃…重大发明
uh, important...inventions.
他…
He, uh, he...
他管我叫他的创意顾问
He calls me his ideas man.
这些设备你都会用吗
Do you know how to use all this stuff?
不全会 可我有 办公椅
Uh, not yet, but I... I have a chair!
喔 喔 喔
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
哈哈
Ha!
早 维克多
Oh, hey, Victor!
他管这儿的卫生
He's the cleaner.
两块三明治摞起来也高过他
He's two sandwiches short of a picnic.
老板要我们削好铅笔
So the pencils all need sharpening,
还有擦干净他明天要穿的靴子
and the boss wants us to polish his boots for tomorrow.
所以你的老板让他的“创意顾问”干这活儿？
So, your big boss calls you his ideas man, huh?
呃 现在是他负责给出创意
Well, uh, he... he has the ideas,
而我只负责叫好
and I think they're great.
但这只是个开始而已
But it's a start!
但你说的没错 维克多
Hey, Victor, you were right for once.
梦想终究会成真的
Dreams can come true!
哦…噢…哦不
Oh! Oh! Oh no!
一位…二位
First position, second,
三位…四位…五位
third, fourth, fifth.
这五种站法就是一切的基础
These five positions form the basis of everything.
一位 二位 三位 四位 五位
First position, second, third, fourth, fifth.
小跳
Now you jump.
一位 二位 三位 四位 五位
First position, second, third, fourth, fifth.
保持住 微笑
And pose and smile!
如果你感到累了 那说明你有进步
It's when you're tired that you start to progress.
你以前…就是…芭蕾舞演员 是不是？
You were a dancer, weren't you?
不许问东问西
No more questions.
再来
Again!
哎呀呀 够不到吧 你得踮起脚尖才能晾上去
Oh, to reach, you might need to stand on your pointes.
找到那个平衡点
Feel the balance.
你的脚趾 就如柳条般柔美
Your toes must be as flexible as willow
又像顽石般坚韧
and hard as a rock.
一位准备！
First position!
不不不 可不能用手擦
Uh-uh-uh! No hands allowed.
什么
What?
试试…这样擦
Try this way.
疼疼疼 要断了啊～
Oh! Stop! Stop! Oh!
你以前就是练过跳舞 对不对
You were a dancer, weren't you?
你说的没错 满意了吗 小侦探
Of course I was a dancer, Sherlock Holmes.
旋转就是控制眩晕感的方法
To pirouette, you must become the mistress of your dizziness.
你得盯住一个点旋转 别转晕了
Stare at a spot, and don't ever lose it.
好的 现在走向我 别让水洒出来
OK, now come to me, and don't spill the water.
哦～～～
Whoa!
干杯吧 干杯
Cheers! Cheers!
♫ 当你领我纵身一跃 ♫
♪ When you ask me to jump ♪
♫ 我才发觉世间多么广阔 ♫
♪ I say how high... ♪
把你的左脚介绍给你的右脚认识认识
Try to introduce your left foot to your right foot.
让它们今后好好相处吧
See if they can get along one day.
♫ 一切皆在眼前 ♫
♪ I'm waiting in line ♪
♫ 现在轮到我了… ♫
♪ But now that it's time... ♪
我给你指条明路
There's a bright future for you
还是去卖蜡烛吧
as a candle seller.
♫ 现在轮到我了 我将全力以赴 ♫
♪ Now that is my turn I'm gonna take what's mine... ♪
一位
First position!
二位 三位
Second! Third!
四位 五位
Fourth, and rest in fifth.
谢谢 孩子们
Thank you, mam'selles.
你进步很大
That was... better!
谢谢
Thanks!
我觉得我可以做那个惊人的跳跃动作了
I'm ready to do that crazy, jumpy thing.
可不是吗 我也觉得我可以加冕为后了
And I'm the Empress Josephine.
我没在开玩笑啊
I am!
绝对不行
Of course you are,
能做和能做好是两码事
but there's a difference between being ready and being ready to do it well.
我们每天练习就是为了做好它
That's why we train every day.
我们的确每天都有练习啊
That's all we've been doing!
想做那个动作 那你先要面对一个问题
And then you'll be ready when you can answer the question,
你为什么要跳舞呢
"Why do you dance?"
我说过啊 那是我的梦想
I've answered it! It's my dream!
哦
Oh! Oh!
啊～
Ow! Ow!
唉
Oh!
我的小姑娘啊 那个惊人的动作叫做“大跳”
By the way, that crazy jumpy thing is called le grand jeté,
以你现在的水准还欠些火候呢
and you're not ready.
你是在练功夫吗 刚才那一招叫什么
Are you doing dance or kung-fu?
一点儿也不好笑
You are SO funny.
这是维克多 我们一起从孤儿院逃出来的
This is Victor. We escaped from the orphanage together.
贵安 美丽的女士 这套裙衬得您清丽脱俗
Hello! I am loving your apron.
那么说 你们晚上要出去玩咯
It seems that you are going out tonight.
没错
Yep!
她要是回来晚了 我会让你的个头再矮上几寸
Bring her back late and you will be six inches smaller.
我们不会玩太晚的 只是出去随便逛逛
Of course, of course, of course!
绝不沾酒 真的
It's a quiet, sober, quiet, sober thing.
布列塔尼的音乐 太棒了
Breton music?Whoa!
噢 抱歉
Whoa! Excuse me!
我好喜欢这音乐啊
I love it here! Whoo!
一起跳吧！
Let's party!
你是喜欢这间酒吧 还是喜欢我
Did you say you loved me or the bar?
耶～～～
Yeah! Whoo!
哇
Whoa!
太赞了
Wow!
哇哦
Whoo!
那是我女朋友！
That's my girlfriend!
你可真走运 小子 哈哈
You're a lucky guy!
太美了
Oh, wow!
哦呜
Oh! Oh!
希望明天上课时 你能稍微优雅一点
I hope that tomorrow you act with a little more dignity.
不过今晚的演出…倒是很不错
Anyway, tonight was...a good performance.
谢谢您
Thank you, sir.
啦啦啦
Whoo! Whoo-hoo!
我不知道你为什么这么开心 但是这样很不错
I have no idea why you're happy, but it is great!
好了 我得回去了
Well, I'd better go in.
我明天就可以去测试了
I've got my audition tomorrow.
好极了 那你睡个好觉 我…
Of course! Sleep well. And I... I...
什么？
What?
我觉得你…
I think you're, uh...
我觉得你很棒
I think you're great.
谢谢
Thanks.
你在干嘛？
What are you doing?
额 没什么
Uh, oh, nothing!
我在做伸展运动
I'm stretching.
嗯没错 再做一个
Yeah, gotta...Ooh, gotta get that one!
嗯…我觉得我是时候走了
OK! Yeah, it's best I leave.
蠢透了，蠢透了，蠢透了
Stupid, stupid, stupid!
嘿 维克多
Hey, Victor!
怎么了
Uh-huh?
我今天玩得很开心
I had the best time.
谢谢你 晚安 菲丽西
Thanks! Goodnight, Felicie.
哦 抱歉 是尊贵的卡米尔小姐
Oh, sorry. Mademoiselle Camille Le Haut.
真是可怜
Wretch!
我要把她送进监狱
I want her put in prison!
她偷了我的生活 我的荣耀 我的名字
She stole my life, my honour and my name!
现在我要夺回来
I want it back!
有点过了
Too much.
我知道了
OK.
你叫什么名字
What is your name?
我叫菲丽西
My name is Felicie Lebras.
我来自布列塔尼地区的一个孤儿院
I come from an orphanage in Brittany.
我并不是故意冒充卡米尔的
I didn't mean to hurt Camille.
我只是想在这儿…
I just wanted to be at the Opera and...
对不起
I'm sorry.
夫人
Madame...
你这个叛徒
You traitor!
你竟然知道这件事
You knew this!
原来是你在背后捅刀子
You stabbed me in the back!
你会被开除的
You are sacked!
不要吵了
Silence!
好了 不喜欢就憋着 这儿我说了算
Alright, like it or lump it, here is my deal.
勒奥女士
Miss Le Haut,
卡米尔明天可以进班练习
you may enter the coryphée class starting tomorrow.
也可以参加《胡桃夹子》的试镜
And you will also be in the auditions for the part in 'The Nutcracker'.
但是我得说清楚
But I want to be clear,
如果你解雇奥黛特女士 我就解雇卡米尔
if you sack Madame Odette, I will sack Camille.
你！
You!
你给这个班开了个坏头
You made a terrible start to the classes,
你已经欺骗了我们
and you have lied and cheated to be here.
但你同时也做了很好的承诺
But you have also shown great promise,
你也很努力的奉献了那么多
and you've worked hard and shown your dedication.
你应该有一个好老师才行
You must have a good teacher.
所以你也可以来试镜
So you may also stay in the auditions.
如果你能公平公正的成功试镜
If you get the part in 'The Nutcracker' fair and square,
你也可以拥有一个芭蕾舞的重要角色
you may become a coryphée too.
如果你失败了 那你必须离开
If you fail to get the part, then you must leave the Opera.
明白了吗
Is that clear?
明白了
Yes.
你也听清楚了吗 女士
Is that also clear to you, madame?
清楚了
Clear.
来自孤儿院的菲丽西
Then, Felicie Lebras from Brittany,
你的未来掌握在你的手里
your future at the Opera is in your hands.
哼
Hmm!
要是她做到了怎么办 妈妈？
What if she's good, Mother?
你必须夺得那个角色 懂了吗
Get that part, do you hear me?
我要复仇
I want vengeance.
把属于我的东西夺回来
I will have it.
她连扫地都那么优雅
She even makes sweeping look graceful.
她是个很好的舞者 不是吗
She was a good dancer, wasn't she?
她不只是一个很好的舞者 她是这一代最好的舞者
Not just a good dancer. The best of her generation.
她是舞台上的一团火
And then there was a fire onstage.
哦
Oh!
这是为什么
What's this for?
为你所做的一切
For everything!
我们可没时间做这些
We don't have time for this.
我们得考虑你的未来
We're talking about your future now.
你只有一个对手 卡米尔
You have only one opponent  Camille.
我见过她跳舞 我知道
I have seen her.I know her.
她的舞技堪称完美
Her technique is perfect,
而且她比我们所看到的还要厉害
and she is stronger than she looks.
她精准而又敏锐
She is precise, she is sharp,
她的字典里没有“输”这个字
and losing is not a word in her vocabulary.
上，下，上，下
Up, down! Up, down!
上，下 再来一次
Up, down! Again!
上，下
Up, down!
我累了
I'm tired.
“累”只属于失败者
'Tired' is for losers!
再来一次 我一定要夺得那个角色
Again! I am going to get that part!
如果你想和她正面对决 那你现在就输定了
If you try to take her down on her turf, you will fail.
你吃得少 营养跟不上
Your diet suffers from eating very little food.
肌肉就没有爆发力
Your muscles are like marshmallows.
就目前而言 理论上你很难取胜
In short, on paper, you're going to get humiliated.
真会安慰人 那我凭什么去赢她啊？
Great pep talk! So, how do I get that part?
你能行 你拥有她梦寐以求的一片拼图
You get the part because you have something she can only dream of
那就是热情
passion!
以它为基础
Build on this.
感受愤怒 欢快 悲伤
Feel your anger and your pain and your sorrow and your joy,
将它尽情融入进你的舞蹈中
and put it all into your dance.
感受音乐的生命力
Live the music, feel it.
每个音符 每段旋律 每首曲子
Every note, every sound, every harmony
都会带动你的身心随之起舞
needs to have your body vibrating
from the end of your hair to the tips of your toes.
到那时 只有到那时 你才有资格胜过她
And then, and only then, will you take her down.
好了 今天要离开的人是
Alright! The person leaving us today is...
嗯～～～
Ahem!
哼
Hmm!
诺拉小姐 这条路你走到头了
This is the end of the road, Miss Nora.
什么路 哦 我被淘汰了 加油 打败她
What road? Oh, I'm finished. I like you. Beat her.
卡米尔和菲丽西 明早八点
Camille and Felicie, tomorrow morning at 8:00am,
我们就会知道你们中的哪一位
we will know which one of you will have the honour
将会成为克拉拉 与罗西塔莫里一起出演胡桃夹子
of dancing Clara in 'The Nutcracker' with Rosita.
希望明天你们可以展现最好的水准
I can only advise you to give everything, ladies.
你的确进步了不少 脏兮兮的小耗子
You've made lots of progress, dirty, little rat,
但明天他们绝对会选我
but tomorrow I am going to be the chosen one.
我看未必
We'll see.
那就放马过来 你整夜练习都没关系
You can work as hard as you like, you can train 24 hours a day,
你永远什么都不是
but you will always be nothing!
我是有身份的人
I am somebody.
有身份是吗 那请你告诉我 你有什么身份
Who exactly? Answer me! Who are you?
你一无是处
You're nothing!
就是个冒名顶替的小耗子
Nothing!
是她错了 知道吗
She's wrong, you know.
你并不孤单
You're not alone.
什么
What?
你还有我呢
You have me.
我们今晚需要做点什么
And I know exactly what we are going to do.
来证明我们心有灵犀
Tonight, to prove our connection,
那就是一场浪漫的约会
we will embark on a little romantic party.
我们今晚七点 一起登上埃菲尔铁塔观看烟花
I offer you the Eiffel Tower. I offer you fireworks. Tonight, 7:00pm
不行 我还得练习呢
I should train.
你不用练习
You don't need to train.
更不用在意你的身份
You don't need to know who you are.
你是独一无二的
You are unique.
再说一次给我听
Say that again?
晚上见
Tonight.
菲丽西 我郑重其事地把它送给你
Felicie, it gives me great pleasure to present to you...
哦不对
No!
维克多 我进了最后一轮选拔
Victor! I'm in the final audition!
真的吗 恭喜啊
Wow! Congratulations!
我也有个好消息 老板终于和我说话了
I have great news too. My boss finally spoke to me!
他说“别再踩我的脚了 你这个讨人厌的小怪胎”
He said, "Get off my foot, you biological mutation!"
是不是挺好
That's good, right?
呃 你可真没品味
Ugh! You have no class.
你怎么就知道我没品味
What, me? No class?
鲁迪就有品位
Rudi has class.
又是他
Rudi again?
怎么 他现在是你的男朋友了吗
What, is he your boyfriend now?
不 但我们…心有灵犀
No! He and I, we're connected.
好好好 我给你品味 还有你要的心有灵犀
OK, OK. You win! I'll give you class and connectivity-ness.
我约你吃晚餐
Dinner! You and me.
我们手持刀啊叉啊 还有餐巾纸什么的
Some knives and forks, napkins.
就今晚七点 埃菲尔铁塔北侧
Uh, 7:00pm, north leg of the Eiffel Tower.
这就算答应了吗
Is that a yes?
是啊 她肯定答应了
Yeah. That's a yes.
坐 我给你看个宝贝
Sit! I've got something for you.
这是我以前的舞鞋 现在它属于你了
They were mine. Now they're yours.
哇哦 谢谢
Wow! Thanks.
不用谢 快吃饭吧 然后我们去训练
OK, enough talking. Eat, and then we practice for tomorrow.
怎么了？
What?
呃 鲁迪约我出去
Well, I'm going out with Rudi.
他说我是独一无二的 没必要再练习了
He says I'm ready. He says I'm unique.
你为什么要跳舞呢
Why do you dance?
别问了好吗
Stop asking me that question!
我还是舞蹈演员的时候 在演出之前训练也从不间断
When I was a dancer, the night before an audition, I trained and then I rested.
鲁迪还在等我呢
Rudi's waiting for me.
别去了
Stay!
才不要 你又不是我妈妈
No! You're not my mom!
对不起
I'm sorry. I wasn't thinking.
算了 你去吧
OK. Go, then.
你看看那飞鸟
Look at the bird.
额…
Um...
再看看我
Now Look at me.
看那飞鸟
Look at the bird.
不 再看看我
No! Hmm? Look at me.
这是我特意为你写的一首诗
This is a poem I composed in your honour.
噢 当然了 一首诗
Ah, of course, a poem.
看啊 那飞鸟 翱翔于云天之上
"Look at the bird! He flies in the sky.“
来去无踪 身心自由
"No-one can trap him."
咕 咕咕 咕咕咕
Coco-co-cocococo
你喜欢吗
Do you like?
这首诗 是挺特别的…
That's, uh...well, original.
我就知道你会喜欢 来吧 小美人 我们走
I know. Thank you. Come on, Minoushka!
去塔顶摘星星咯
Let us go to the very top! To the stars!
好了 马汀 我们排练一遍
OK, Matty, we practise.
音乐起 古典音乐
Music, please! Classical!
好吧 可我不怎么擅长古典音乐
OK, but that's not my musical comfort zone.
喔 快停下 不行不行
Oh, stop! Stop, stop, stop!
还是乡村音乐吧 不过要轻柔浪漫
We'll go Breton, but soft and romantic.
一定要震撼到她
This will blow her away.
等她来了 一定喜出望外
She arrives, she giggles.
而我则深沉又神秘地拿出音乐盒
I am looking dark and mysterious. I give her the music box.
她一定会这样 哦～人家好感动啊～
She's... "Oh! Oh!" Overwhelmed!
我不是很了解女孩子
Uh, I don't know much about girls.
应该说我完全搞不懂她们
Frankly, they are a mystery to me.
但我很确定她今晚不会来了
But I do know that this one's not coming.
你还太小还不明白 她一定会来的
Young, innocent fool! Of course she will come!
我已经闻到了她的香水味
I can already smell her perfume.
哦 不
Oh, no!
是乞丐啊 恶！
Oh, beggars! Ugh!
巴黎怎么到处都是这种人 恶心
Paris is infested with beggars! Yuck!
但是…
But...
别害怕
Don't be afraid.
但我…
But...
你别说话
Quiet! Follow me.
我根据哥萨克舞蹈中的动作 自创了一套拳法
Have no fear, I have developed a fighting technique based on Cossack dancing.
你别胡闹了
Don't be ridiculous!
好了 够了 听我说 他是我的朋友
OK, stop right there! He's my friend!
你在开玩笑么
Oh, is this some kind of joke?
不 他叫维克多 我们从小就认识
No! This is Victor. We grew up together.
天呐 你成功逗笑了我
Oh, my! This is funny.
朋友 哈？
Friends, huh?
只是朋友的话 你怎么一脸羞愧
If we're friends, why are you looking so ashamed?
我没有一脸羞愧啊
I'm not looking ashamed.
明明就有 你真让我失望 菲丽西
Oh, yes, you are! I feel sorry for you, Felicie.
哦 你在妒忌
Oh! You're jealous.
才没有 你进巴黎歌剧院到底想干嘛
No! Ever since you started at the Opera, who are you trying to be?
就为了和这个一身毛的大蒜苗鬼混吗
Mixing with this big, hairy asparagus?
你真可悲
You're so sad.
喔喔喔 矮矬穷
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
我只要动动手指就能把你打晕
I could knock you out with one flick of my tiny finger,
可这样会弄脏我的手指 洗都洗不干净
but that would make my finger dirty and smelly.
我是很脏没错 可是我从来不穿娘炮才穿的紧身裤
So, I'm dirty, but at least I don't spend my day in tights!
你们不要闹了
I can't believe this!
她是我的女神
She is my muse.
是吗 那她也是我的女神
Yeah, well, she is my whatever-you-just-said, too,
我们先认识的 你这个大蒜苗
with knobs on, asparagus!
住手
Stop!
你们两个白痴
You're both idiots!
好吧 那再会了
OK. Well, goodbye, then.
再见
Well, goodbye.
这招可真够阴险的
That is so low!
噢 糟了 最后一轮选拔
Oh, no! The audition!
我敢保证这次的…
I'm sure this...
看着点儿
Watch it!
《胡桃夹子》的演出肯定…
..production of 'Nutcracker' is going to...
借过
Excuse me!
嘿
Hey!
好极了 堪称完美
Bravo! Bravo!
谢谢你的表演 卡米尔小姐
Thank you, mademoiselle.
那位还没来 看来没必要再比了
The orphan is late. It's over.
好吧 既然菲丽西不想来
Well, as Felicie did not deign to show up for the audition,
那么就让卡米尔和罗西塔一同登台
it is Camille who will dance with Rosita.
等等 等等 请等一下 我来了
Wait! Wait! I'm here!
求求您 让我跳吧
Please, please let me dance.
已经太迟了 你不懂规矩吗
It's over! Don't you understand?
请您 坐下
Sit down!
我…我很抱歉
I-I apologise.
你睡过头了？
Did you sleep?
也不是
Not much.
那昨晚训练了吗
Did you train yesterday?
没有
No.
为什么
Why?
音乐 起
Alright, music!
哼
Hmm!
再来一遍
Start again.
这不合规矩
She fell! She's eliminated!
我说 再来一遍
Start again!
我们有言在先
You remember our deal?
卡米尔 《胡桃夹子》中的克拉拉由你出演
Camille, you will have the honour of dancing Clara in 'The Nutcracker'.
你以为这样就算完了吗 小耗子
Did you think it would end here, little rat?
不 放开我 不要
No! Let me go! No!
哦 不
Oh, no!
别走 别走
Please! Please!
奥黛特 不
Odette! No!
奥黛特
Odette!
菲丽西
Felicie!
真可怜 你们再也没法见面了吧
You will never see her again.
当然 你也该走人了
And, of course, you're sacked.
立正
Stop!
菲丽西这次又去哪儿了
Where is Felicie?
咳
Ahem!
我在这儿
I'm here.
喔 哦 好吧 很好
Oh! Well, uh, good.
看她的样子好像丢了魂一样
She's lost her spirit.
得得得 打起精神来 你帮过什么忙
Tut-tut-tut! Pull yourself together, you big fool!
我知道你在想维克多去哪儿了 我也很想他
I know. I miss him too.
♫ 你是否已经敞开心扉 我有些秘密想要透露 ♫
♪ Have you told me all? I've got things to say ♪
♫ 嘿 听得到吗 ♫
♪ Hey, I'm talking to you ♪
♫ 我们本应该一起创造精彩 设想未来 ♫
♪ We got things to do We got plans to make ♪
♫ 多希望你能陪伴我身旁 ♫
♪ And I wanna take you with me ♪
♫ 伴我身旁 ♫
♪ Yeah, I wanna take you with me... ♪
♫ 可你一朝离去 我便心慌意乱 ♫
♪ But a far-off gaze is wide in me ♪
♫ 你可知晓 ♫
♪ Can you feel it? ♪
♫ 你可知晓我心中难安 ♫
♪ And if you can't tell I'm a restless girl ♪
♫ 无论你听到多少谎言 ♫
♪ What are you hearing? ♪
♫ 请将流言 抛诸脑后 ♫
♪ Pack it all away Pack it all in one suitcase ♪
♫ 梦已成真 身获自由 ♫
♪ I got all I need, all I need to be free ♪
♫ 请将流言 抛诸脑后 ♫
♪ Pack it all away Pack it all in one suitcase ♪
♫ 梦已成真 身获自由 ♫
♪ I got all I need, all I need to be free ♪
♫ 请将流言 抛诸脑后 ♫
♪ Pack it all away Pack it all in one suitcase ♪
♫ 梦已成真 身获自由 ♫
♪ I got all I need, all I need ♪
♫ 梦已成真 我心飞翔 ♫
♪ I'm flying ♪
♫ 请将流言 抛诸脑后 ♫
♪ Pack it all away Pack it all in one suitcase ♪
♫ 梦已成真 身获自由 ♫
♪ I got all I need, all I need to be free ♪
♫ 请将流言 抛诸脑后 ♫
♪ Pack it all away Pack it all in one suitcase ♪
♫ 梦已成真 身获自由 ♫
♪ I got all I need, all I need ♪
♫ 梦已成真 我心飞翔 ♫
♪ I'm flying ♪
我是想逃跑没错
OK, I was escaping,
可又被您捉到了 我真傻
but it's stupid, and you caught me.
真是对不起 我马上回房间去
So, a big sorry to you, and I'll just go back to the dorm.
跟我来 快点儿
This way, quick!
嗯？
Huh?
喔～～～
Whoo! Whoo-hoo!
谢谢您
Thank you!
快去吧
Go now.
我来帮您吧
Let me help you.
您需要我 我会打扫
You need me. I can clean.
我可以打扫得非常干净
'Squeaky Clean' is my middle name.
不 是我需要您
In fact, I need you.
我再也不想离开您了
I wanna stay with you.
对不起 我好想您
I'm so sorry! I really missed you!
我也是
Me too.
来吧
Come on.
莫里小姐把阁楼的房间安排给我了
Merante has given me a room in the attic.
有个角落可以留给你
There's a little corner for you.
我们早晨六点开始工作 午休时间一小时
Work starts at 6:00am. One hour for lunch.
早晨六点？
6:00am?
我发誓 他不在这儿
I promise, he is not here.
那他什么时候回来呢 拜托
Do you know when he's coming back? Please!
好吧 那…
Well, actually...
噢
Ow!
不 我不知道
Nope! I don't know that.
那好吧
So...
请帮我转告他 对不起
Will you please tell him that I'm sorry?
我不该那样对待他
I've been unkind and foolish
那样做真的太蠢了 太不知好歹了
and silly and stupid.
也很无礼
And rude.
没错也很无礼
告诉他我们是最好的朋友 永远都是
Tell Victor that he's my best friend ever.
哦…呃…
Oh! Uh...
那是我的第三只手
That's my other hand.
我有三只手 没毛病
I have three hands, actually.
谢谢
Thank you.
不客气
You're welcome.
你走吧
Goodbye, then.
再见 维克多
Bye, Victor.
那不是他 他真的出去了
That wasn't him. He is not here.
真看不出来维克多还有这样的本事
Victor has worked a miracle! Who'd have thought?
他看起来傻兮兮的
He just has the look of a total nitwit.
他再也不会理我了
He doesn't wanna speak to me ever again.
他会的
He will.
不对 不对 不对
No, no, no!
又来了
Here we go!
停！ 毫无内涵
Stop! As cold as lard!
勒奥小姐 公演在即
Miss Le Haut, you perform tonight
为什么我在你的舞姿中看不到一丝丝的感情
and so far, we have no emotion!
可是我每个动作都符合您的技术标准啊
But I'm doing exactly the steps you told me.
我没有在跟你谈技巧
It's not enough to do the steps.
你的舞蹈里 愤怒 欢快 悲伤 一样都没有
Find some anger or some pain or some love, but find something!
她缺的就是这个 今晚见分晓
She lacks this. Tonight will make that clear.
好了 你继续看吧 我去打扫别的地方了
OK, I'm going to do the stairs in the lobby. You can finish here.
好的
OK.
干嘛 还给我
Leave it. Give it back.
我真傻 第一次丢的时候干嘛不用点劲儿呢
Silly me! I didn't throw it hard enough the first time.
同样的错误 别再犯第二回
Don't make the same mistake.
你这就走了？是怕被我羞辱吗？
Why are you leaving? Scared of being humiliated?
我想你还需要多练练
Looks like you need more training.
这一字马你开的挺吃力吧
You are nowhere near ready.
是时候让你见识见识科班出身的专业芭蕾舞演员了
I'm going to show you what a real dancer looks like.
哦哈 原来你是专业芭蕾舞演员啊
Are you sure about that?
闭嘴
Quiet!
今晚台下将坐满观众
Tonight these seats will be full.
他们都会为我的演出倾倒 崇拜我
Paris will be looking at me, adoring me!
我看未必
Or not.
我说过了
I already told you!
你谁也不是 小耗子 你成不了什么角儿
You are nothing. You will always be nothing!
那只有试过才知道
Only one way to find out.
就现在 就在这儿 敢接招吗
Right here, right now.
♫ 我已接管舞台 成为主宰 ♫
♪ It's time for me to take it  I'm the boss right now... ♪
♫ 别想自欺欺人 跪下看好 ♫
♪ Not gonna fake it Not when you go down ♪
♫ 这盘游戏是我坐庄 你尽可一试 ♫
♪ 'Cause this is my game   And you better come to play ♪
♫ 我曾屏息以待 今朝放手一搏 ♫
♪ I used to hold my freak back    Now I'm letting go ♪
♫ 我意已决 好戏正要开场 ♫
♪ I make my own choice   Yeah I run this show ♪
哦 我的天哪 对决开始了！
Oh, my God! BATTLE!
♫ 灯光聚焦 ♫
♪ So, leave the lights on ♪
♫ 你已无法将我左右 ♫
♪ No, you can't make me behave ♪
♫ 你污蔑我乱魂失智 ♫
♪ So, you say I'm complicated ♪
♫ 根本就是疯癫狂妄 ♫
♪ That I must be out of my mind ♪
♫ 欺我诳我 说我不自量 ♫
♪ But you had me underrated Rated, rated Oh, oh, oh♪
♫ 有何不可 ♫
♪ What's wrong with being... ♪
♫ 做自信的我 何须迷惘 ♫
♪ What's wrong with being confident? ♪
♫ 有何不可 ♫
♪ What's wrong with being... ♪
♫ 我自行其是 任人飞短流长 ♫
♪ What's wrong with being confident? ♪
你能行的
You can do it!
两位都跳得不错
Impressive, ladies.
但我还有个问题要问你们
But let me ask you both an important question.
你们为什么要跳舞呢
Why do you dance?
我跳舞是因为…是因为…因为…
I dance because... I dance because... because...
我妈逼我的
..my mother makes me.
因为跳舞一直是我的梦想 是生命的一部分
Because it's always been a part of my life.
我还在襁褓中就和妈妈一起跳舞
It was there with my mom when I was a baby,
而现在我有了奥黛特
and it's here now, thanks to Odette.
我爱跳舞 舞蹈让我的人生有了意义
It allows me to live, to be myself.
让她跳好了
She should dance.
勒奥小姐 你既诚实又勇敢
That was very honest, Miss Le Haut, and brave.
若你仍愿意留在我的剧团里 我将非常欢迎
You have a future at the Opera, if you wish it.
菲丽西 今晚的《胡桃夹子》将由你来演
Felicie, tonight, you dance 'The Nutcracker'.
恭喜你了
Great job.
做的太棒了 我的小甜心们
Well done, my sweetness!
精彩绝伦
OK. Bravo, bravo. Oh, bravo!
太好了
Yes! Yes!
完成了
Voilà!
这就是第三代“鸡翼”
I call them Pigeon Wings! -
哇 真棒
Wow! Great!
不过我不是很想试用它
But I'm not sure I want to test them.
有点冒险精神好不好 马汀
Live dangerously, Matty!
我可以向你保证它能基本正常地运行
I promise you they will almost certainly work.
哦～
Oh!
这下可好了
This is nice!
马汀 给我们挪挪地方好吗
Matty, can you give us some privacy?
什么时候？
When?
马汀 出去啦
Matty, privacy!
噢 这就出去
Oh, now. OK!
我今晚在歌剧院演出
I'm dancing tonight at the Opera.
我希望你能来看
I want you to be there.
真的吗
Really?
没错
Really.
菲丽西 我喜欢你
I like you, Felicie.
你现在搞得我哭笑不得 手足无措的
You make me laugh and cry at the same time.
你可真是个怪胎
You're a weirdo!
哒哒哒 你救不了他
Tut-tut-tut! You cannot help him.
你先是欺骗我的女儿
First you deceive my daughter.
又窃取她的身份
Then you take her identity!
妈妈 住手
Mom, stop!
现在还想盗走我们的荣誉
Now you try and take our honor and our future?
妈妈 不
Mother!
你以为离间了我们母女 我还会轻易地放过你吗
Do you think you can turn my daughter against me and get away with it?
你骗过我女儿 却骗不了我
Ah! No-one cheats me!
妈妈 你吓到她了 不要
Mother! You scared her! Stop!
上回她迟到时 后果很严重
The last time she was this late, it did not end well.
啊
Aaah!
我怎么看到 有两个马汀啊
Hey, it's Matty and his twin sister!
发生了什么
What happened?
有位可怕的夫人追着你女朋友上了青春女神像 要杀了她
There's a big, scary lady chasing your girl up the statue, trying to kill her.
什么
What?
我快要吓死了 根本拦不住她
And, also, I wet myself.
快 快去救她
Come on! Quickly! Save her!
马汀 准备第三代“鸡翼”
Matty, the Pigeon Wings!
这就是你今天可以得到的唯一一顶皇冠
This is the only crown you will touch today,
恐怕你要出点儿什么意外 缺席今晚的演出了
victim of a terrible accident on the night of your debut.
就像奥黛特一样 从此告别芭蕾了
You will have something to share with Odette. Both of you used to be dancers.
菲丽西 我来了
Felicie!
起飞吧
Let go! Oh!
啊偶 还好
Uh-oh! OK!
啊哦
Uh-oh.
菲丽西
Felicie!
哈哈哈
Ha, ha, ha!
不
No!
哇
Whoo!
别担心 菲丽西 维克多在此为您效劳 使命必达
Felicie, don't worry. We'll be on time!
飞得更高 耶！
Higher! YES!
使命必达
We will be on time!
我觉得你这个玩意儿该装个刹车什么的
In version three, it might be a good idea to work on some brakes.
哈哈 你就不能说点好话 夸我一下吗
Can't you just say that I've invented something and it worked?
好啊
I can.
那你倒是说啊
Then say it!
维克多弗朗索瓦格沙维耶氏
Victor François Xavier the First,
你是个伟大的发明家
you're a great inventor.
谢谢
Thank you.
现在你准备好了
You're ready.
用心去跳 菲丽西 用你那颗热爱芭蕾的心
Then dance from right here.
算你赢了
You won the bet.
你先实现了你的梦想
You made your dream come true.
♫ 我曾梦见我们冲破束缚 ♫
♪ I had a dream, was it real? We crossed the line and it was...♪
♫ 终于如愿盛放 ♫
♪ I can't make it stop  Give me all you got...  ♪
让巴黎为我们倾倒吧
Let's set Paris on fire.
♫ 想要全情投入 ♫
♪ I want to go all the way Take me to emotion... ♪
♫ 再无私心杂念 ♫
♪ I want to go all the way Show me devotion ♪
♫ 从此一同 ♫
♪ And take me all the way, all the way ♪
♫ 哦哦哦 ♫
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♫ 冲破云霄 摆脱束缚 ♫
♪ I wanna cut through the clouds Break the ceiling ♪
♫ 你我同台 翩翩起舞 ♫
♪ I wanna dance on the roof, you and me alone ♪
♫ 渴望如此恣情 ♫
♪ I wanna cut to the feeling ♪
♫ 渴望如此尽意 ♫
真不愧是我的女朋友
That really is my girlfriend.
♫ 想要一同 与天使共舞 ♫
♪ Play with the angels ♪
♫ 渴望如此恣情 ♫
♪ I wanna cut to the feeling ♪
♫ 渴望如此尽意 ♫
♫ 我渴望这种感觉 ♫
♪ I wanna cut to the feeling ♪
[请看到最后哦]
了不起的菲丽西